A brand new day has dawned
Good morning, lay hee! It's time to wake up!
Over all the hills and even through the woods,
Take a deep breath and relax
Give all your worries the flick
(Gently, softly)
and leave them out to air atop a tree
and bid them goodbye, hey!
Lively, energetic and full of life
Happy as happy can be, we sing gently with a ho ho ho.
And friendly,
as close as two friends can be!
So come join this song, lay hee!
Cyalume change!
Hey little goat! (Baa baa baa) Hey little bird! (Tweet tweet tweet)
Hey little pig! (oink oink oink) Hey, horses and cows! (Neigh, moo)
Hey little frog! (Ribbit ribbit) Hey little duck! (quack quack)
And hello to you, too! (heigh ho!) Come join us, everyone!
Lively, energetic and full of life
Happy as happy can be, we sing gently with a ho ho ho.
And friendly,
as close as two friends can be!
Come join this song, lay hee!
Pick up your feet, raise your voice, and come join this song, lay hee!